<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strongest Boss System on Aisan Translated Novels</title>
    <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strongest Boss System on Aisan Translated Novels</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter1 the great villain system</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>PS: Due to individual reasons in this book, all characters involved in the original work need to be obscured or their names changed.It&amp;rsquo;s not Author - kun&amp;rsquo;s deliberate mistake. Please forgive me.
In the shabby hut, the dim light radiates hazy brilliance, and only a thin figure can be vaguely seen crouching beside the table.
Su Xin&amp;rsquo;er very cautiously holds half of the mouldy steamed bread and swallows.
&amp;ldquo;No! I cannot eat it, this is for the elder brother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter2  can kill people, is the sword!</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>The next morning, Su Xin woke up early and saw Xin&amp;rsquo;er, who was still asleep, quietly covered her with a quilt.
Opening the rice jar, Su Xin&amp;rsquo;s heart felt a little convulsive pain when he saw the rice jar with only a dozen grains of rice inside.
Staggering out of the door, Su Xin planned to find something to make a sword.
Get Jing Wuming&amp;rsquo;s Quick Sword, he also need to have a sword first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter3  If you want to destroy it, you must  make it crazy  first</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Changning Prefecture 49 Blocks, although Long Music Block is the poorest Fang City, but it is not all slums. At least one street is pretty good. It is called Happy Forest.
As the name suggests, Happy Forest is a place where people are happy,On a small street, there are hundreds of gambling halls, restaurants, brothels, and inn.
With this Happy Forest, you can feed dozens of Gangsters from Flying Eagle Gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter4  What I&#39;m better at is the right hand</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Outside the drunk moon building, Su Xin looks at the carved beams and painted rafters,Decorated with gilded, it looks luxurious and incomparable architecture exclaimed.
Compared with the grottoes of long music block,It&amp;rsquo;s almost like another world here.
&amp;ldquo;Stop! This is already our Flying Eagle Gang Packing Yard.Go elsewhere.Seeing Su Xin entering Drunk Moon Building, a young Flying Eagle Gang gangster quickly stopped him.
Su Xin said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m here for Liu Sandao.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter5 Sophistry</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>There are actually only four sites belonging to flying eagle Gang, including long music blocks that have fallen to the extreme.
As one of the 13 great leaders of flying eagle Gang, Third Master tiger is the kind with relatively strong strength. His territory is one third of the happy intent block.
Compared with the long music block, the happy intent block is much more prosperous. The streets are full of people, and there are endless pedestrians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter6 Mission accomplished </title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>When Su Xin went out, a middle-aged man in his 40s, dressed as a literati, came out from behind the screen. TSK TSK sighed: &amp;ldquo;this youngster is really unusual. This intention is terrifying. He is not 20 years old, is he? Third master, do you mind giving happy forest to him? Not afraid of him becoming another Chen Dao? &amp;quot;
&amp;ldquo;Afraid? I&amp;rsquo;m afraid he won&amp;rsquo;t be another Chen Dao! &amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter7 Da Xumi sword style</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-7/</guid>
      <description>The next morning, Su Xin woke up and saw Xin&amp;rsquo;er sleeping there like a pig. She didn&amp;rsquo;t disturb her, but went straight out of the yard.
There are two clever gang members arranged by Huang Bingcheng outside.
Originally, Huang Bingcheng arranged for four people, but Su Xin felt that it was unnecessary, so he left two people and two others to watch the night.
Seeing Su Xin coming out, the two guild members hurriedly saluted: &amp;ldquo;boss su.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter8 It&#39;s cruel to kill. Beat the It&#39;s cruel to kill. Beat the disabled</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>There is only one medicine shop in the whole Changle square, which is next to the joyful forest.
Other people think changlefang is a slum. It has little oil and water. They are unwilling to open a drugstore here.
Happy forest is rich, but how many people can be sick in a street? To open a drugstore here is only to lose money.
But the manager of Wangji pharmacy think to be longer than others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter9 reform</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-9/</guid>
      <description>Half an hour later, the owners of the casinos, brothels, restaurants and inns in the joyful forest were all gathered in the hall of zuiyue building, bowing their hands to each other to say hello. They all looked bitter.
In their business, it&amp;rsquo;s normal to pay regular money to gangs every month, but have you ever seen it paid three times a month?
At the beginning of this month, jolly forest originally belonged to green bamboo gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter10 reject a face-saving offer </title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-10/</guid>
      <description>All the bosses were thinking in secret, when suddenly came two sneers.
People look up, the voice is still boss Huang.
&amp;ldquo;Boss Su, your idea is really good, but it&amp;rsquo;s a little unrealistic.
Businessmen chase profits, but also to their extreme, if we here according to what you say to do, in advance will indeed attract a lot of customers.
But if the people in changdefang react and follow our example, the advantages of the region are revealed immediately, and we still can&amp;rsquo;t rob others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>