<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strongest Boss System on Aisan Translated Novels</title>
    <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strongest Boss System on Aisan Translated Novels</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter1 the great villain system</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>PS: Due to individual reasons in this book, all characters involved in the original work need to be obscured or their names changed.It&amp;rsquo;s not Author - kun&amp;rsquo;s deliberate mistake. Please forgive me.
In the shabby hut, the dim light radiates hazy brilliance, and only a thin figure can be vaguely seen crouching beside the table.
Su Xin&amp;rsquo;er very cautiously holds half of the mouldy steamed bread and swallows.
&amp;ldquo;No! I cannot eat it, this is for the elder brother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter2  can kill people, is the sword!</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>The next morning, Su Xin woke up early and saw Xin&amp;rsquo;er, who was still asleep, quietly covered her with a quilt.
Opening the rice jar, Su Xin&amp;rsquo;s heart felt a little convulsive pain when he saw the rice jar with only a dozen grains of rice inside.
Staggering out of the door, Su Xin planned to find something to make a sword.
Get Jing Wuming&amp;rsquo;s Quick Sword, he also need to have a sword first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter3  If you want to destroy it, you must  make it crazy  first</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Changning Prefecture 49 Blocks, although Long Music Block is the poorest Fang City, but it is not all slums. At least one street is pretty good. It is called Happy Forest.
As the name suggests, Happy Forest is a place where people are happy,On a small street, there are hundreds of gambling halls, restaurants, brothels, and inn.
With this Happy Forest, you can feed dozens of Gangsters from Flying Eagle Gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter4  What I&#39;m better at is the right hand</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Outside the drunk moon building, Su Xin looks at the carved beams and painted rafters,Decorated with gilded, it looks luxurious and incomparable architecture exclaimed.
Compared with the grottoes of long music block,It&amp;rsquo;s almost like another world here.
&amp;ldquo;Stop! This is already our Flying Eagle Gang Packing Yard.Go elsewhere.Seeing Su Xin entering Drunk Moon Building, a young Flying Eagle Gang gangster quickly stopped him.
Su Xin said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m here for Liu Sandao.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter5 Sophistry</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>There are actually only four sites belonging to flying eagle Gang, including long music blocks that have fallen to the extreme.
As one of the 13 great leaders of flying eagle Gang, Third Master tiger is the kind with relatively strong strength. His territory is one third of the happy intent block.
Compared with the long music block, the happy intent block is much more prosperous. The streets are full of people, and there are endless pedestrians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter6 Mission accomplished </title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>When Su Xin went out, a middle-aged man in his 40s, dressed as a literati, came out from behind the screen. TSK TSK sighed: &amp;ldquo;this youngster is really unusual. This intention is terrifying. He is not 20 years old, is he? Third master, do you mind giving happy forest to him? Not afraid of him becoming another Chen Dao? &amp;quot;
&amp;ldquo;Afraid? I&amp;rsquo;m afraid he won&amp;rsquo;t be another Chen Dao! &amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter7 Da Xumi sword style</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-7/</guid>
      <description>The next morning, Su Xin woke up and saw Xin&amp;rsquo;er sleeping there like a pig. She didn&amp;rsquo;t disturb her, but went straight out of the yard.
There are two clever gang members arranged by Huang Bingcheng outside.
Originally, Huang Bingcheng arranged for four people, but Su Xin felt that it was unnecessary, so he left two people and two others to watch the night.
Seeing Su Xin coming out, the two guild members hurriedly saluted: &amp;ldquo;boss su.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter8 It&#39;s cruel to kill. Beat the It&#39;s cruel to kill. Beat the disabled</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>There is only one medicine shop in the whole Changle square, which is next to the joyful forest.
Other people think changlefang is a slum. It has little oil and water. They are unwilling to open a drugstore here.
Happy forest is rich, but how many people can be sick in a street? To open a drugstore here is only to lose money.
But the manager of Wangji pharmacy think to be longer than others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter9 reform</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-9/</guid>
      <description>Half an hour later, the owners of the casinos, brothels, restaurants and inns in the joyful forest were all gathered in the hall of zuiyue building, bowing their hands to each other to say hello. They all looked bitter.
In their business, it&amp;rsquo;s normal to pay regular money to gangs every month, but have you ever seen it paid three times a month?
At the beginning of this month, jolly forest originally belonged to green bamboo gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter10 reject a face-saving offer </title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-10/</guid>
      <description>All the bosses were thinking in secret, when suddenly came two sneers.
People look up, the voice is still boss Huang.
&amp;ldquo;Boss Su, your idea is really good, but it&amp;rsquo;s a little unrealistic.
Businessmen chase profits, but also to their extreme, if we here according to what you say to do, in advance will indeed attract a lot of customers.
But if the people in changdefang react and follow our example, the advantages of the region are revealed immediately, and we still can&amp;rsquo;t rob others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter11 greedy Third master tiger</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-11/</guid>
      <description>In the house of happy intent block Third Master tiger.
Third master tiger took the list given to him by Huang Bingcheng and smiled without saying a word. The middle-aged scribe beside him was holding the folding fan tightly, with a look of horror on his face.
&amp;ldquo;Adviser Li, how about my adopted son?&amp;rdquo; Asked the third master tiger, looking up.
Opening the folding fan fiercely, adviser Li said in a deep voice: &amp;ldquo;ruthless, spicy, thoughtful, the most important thing is to know how to advance and retreat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter12 change of the happy forest </title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-12/</guid>
      <description>As a loyal and old customer of happy forest, childe sun has just arrived, and someone will report that the boss Liu personally of drunk moon building will come out to meet him.
&amp;ldquo;Ha ha ha ha, childe sun hasn&amp;rsquo;t come this month. All the girls in drunk moon building want to die of you. Today, I specially left two trumps for childe sun.&amp;rdquo; Said boss Liu with a warm smile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter13 Wealth attracts people </title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-13/</guid>
      <description>In the house of happy intent block Third Master tiger.
Third master tiger plays with the silver sent by Su Xin, and there is a trace of smiling expression on the corner of his mouth.
&amp;ldquo;Adviser Li, how did I get it from the adopted son? It&amp;rsquo;s only over a month. I&amp;rsquo;ll get 30000 silver taels back. Hahaha! &amp;quot; Third master tiger laughed.
It is said that this man can&amp;rsquo;t be compared with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter14 sudden and unexpected disaster</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-14/</guid>
      <description>In Changning Province, three gangs, four unions, green bamboo gang and flying eagle gang are the weakest two, and the twogang face is also a close match.
Although green bamboo Gang lost the battle of happy forest, they didn&amp;rsquo;t lose much manpower in fact. It can be said that they actually let the happy forest out on their own initiative.
After all, the previous Happy Forest can really not have any profit, a month at the top of the day to collect 4, 500 taels of monthly money is also good, in order to such a place to fight to the death with Flying Eagle Gang, why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter15 brutal reality</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-15/</guid>
      <description>Master Happy Intention Block Third Tiger&amp;rsquo;s house, this time Su Xin does not have to announce, the two gangster doormen directly let Su Xin and Huang Bingcheng in.
To be able to create such a momentum in Happy Forest, even if Su Xin is not the adopted son, of Third Tiger, they deserve their respect.
In the living room, third tiger is sitting on the main seat, as if knowing Su Xin is coming, and adviser Li is standing behind him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter16 Inspiring people&#39;s hearts </title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-16/</guid>
      <description>Su Xin&amp;rsquo;s words immediately stunned all the people present, even though Huang Bingcheng, who had vaguely guessed Su Xin&amp;rsquo;s plan, was still the case.
Who is Great Chieftain Dai Chong of green bamboo gang? That&amp;rsquo;s the Jianghu boss , who has thousands of subordinate. I&amp;rsquo;m afraid he spends time with Jianghu than you Su Xin&amp;rsquo;s old.
And Dai Chong&amp;rsquo;s identity does not rely on relationships, it is a one-size-fits-all fight, want to kill Dai Chong, which in their view is a fantasy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter17 Assassination</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-17/</guid>
      <description>The Paradise Square, Li Huai with Suxin Jinsheng gambling ran straight away.
Dai Chong likes to gamble, Huang Bingcheng has found out, these days Dai Chong every day in Jinsheng gambling shop.
And Zhang Hong, who knew he had caused trouble, was also waiting with Dai Chong ,to curry favor with his boss.
Su Xin may have been to Yongle Square before, but his memory is a little blurred after the trip, so he is now looking at everything around him, not curious, but to choose the best escape route after the assassination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter18 Fast sword </title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-18/</guid>
      <description>Li Huai&amp;rsquo;s sudden killing, suddenly let Green Bamboo Gang&amp;rsquo;s those gang members a little in a hurry.
Most of them just have the level of street fighting. How many of them have seen the scene of killing and seeing blood?
Li Huai in the hands of the short sword stabbing, picking, chopping, plucking, ruthless, and stop the gang member to support
&amp;ldquo;Bunch of waste!&amp;rdquo;
See this scene of Dai Chong almost angry vomiting blood, did not expect their own people so useless, so many people together, unexpectedly can not stop each other a person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter19 Big things happen</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-19/</guid>
      <description>Su Xin and Li Huai carry their heads back to joyful forest, where Li Qing and others have been looking forward to.
Originally, Su Xin arranged for them to be break up, but Su Xin and Li Huai were too quick to do so. Before green bamboo gang&amp;rsquo;s men and horses came, they brought back the heads of Dai Chong and Zhang Hong, and did not give them a chance to hunt them down at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter20 Interrogation</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-20/</guid>
      <description>Sunyi block。
Walking on the street with Dai Chong&amp;rsquo;s head, Huang Bingcheng felt awkward.
The moment before is still the majestic green bamboo gang big leader, this moment actually was packed in the box, becomes someone&amp;rsquo;s trophy, this kind of feeling lets Huang Bingcheng some inexplicable sigh.
Looking at the front of the stable Su Xin, Huang Bingcheng really can not think of, this boss how to get so much self-confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter21 acting school</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-21/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;because I&amp;rsquo;m from Flying Eagle Gang, that&amp;rsquo;s why I chose to assassinate Dai Chong!&amp;rdquo;
Su Xin looked passionate: &amp;ldquo;Dai rushed to kill my brother, provoking me Flying Eagle Gang, is unpardonable!&amp;rdquo; I Suxin can be where I am today, all by the cultivation of Flying Eagle Gang, humiliating me Flying Eagle Gang, is insulting me Suxin! &amp;quot;
&amp;ldquo;then can you consider the consequences of this?&amp;rdquo; Dong Chengwu snorted coldly.
Su Xin patted himself on the chest: &amp;ldquo;my parents died early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter22 Intrigue and lottery</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-22/</guid>
      <description>On the way back, Master Li learned from Third master tiger what had happened in Main Hall, and he could not help but pat his thighs.
Su Xin played this trick, ah, the hard life is to turn the trial meeting against him into a game of fighting for power and profit within the Flying Eagle Gang.
From the beginning, Su Xin did not distinguish for himself, but put himself in a hero position who did not hesitate to fight with green bamboo gang for the sake of his brother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter23 Martial arts dominate</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-23/</guid>
      <description>Nothing good came out of the two intermediate raffles, and Su Xin lacked some confidence in the third raffle.
But there was nothing technical about this kind of luck, so Su Xin gritted his teeth and took it out for the third time.
The roulette turned slowly and was pleasantly surprised to fall into the kung fu column, this time appearing on the big screen as a young swordsman.
Dressed in a big red robe, tall and beautiful, at first glance, he looked like a handsome young man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter24 Imparting merit method</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-24/</guid>
      <description>In hallway&amp;rsquo;s single room, Su Xin sat in a chair drinking tea, and soon Huang Bingcheng came in with Li Huai pushing the door.
&amp;ldquo;Boss.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Boss Su.&amp;rdquo;
That Su boss is Li Huai shout, but let Huang Bingcheng a good surprise.
When he first met this guy, he was very arrogant, and even made it clear that he would not listen to Suxin&amp;rsquo;s orders. How can he shout boss Su now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There is no absolute waste of martial arts.</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-25/</guid>
      <description>Instruct subordinate helps internal merit,. This is what Su Xin decided yesterday.
His strength is still too weak, although he can kill Dai Chong, but that is only because of the sneak attack assassination reasons, hit Dai Chong a surprise.
If there is another occasion, it is still unknown who wins or loses.
And this time to Main Hall, to see the three Hall Master and unfathomable Gang Master,Su Xin very clear, their current strength compared with them, or too far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The sadness of the people at the bottom</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-26/</guid>
      <description>After discussing the teaching of subordinate brother martial skill, Su Xin turned around, saw that there was nothing to do, and was ready to go back.
Hallway is guarded, his courtyard is close to Happy Forest, and as soon as something happens, someone will come to report.
Moreover, with the current prestige of Su Xin, it is estimated that few people dare to cause trouble.
Even Third master tiger and Hall Master Dong Chengwu, who are unhappy with him, won&amp;rsquo;t come and mess with him at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>