<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strongest Boss System on Aisan Translated Novels</title>
    <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strongest Boss System on Aisan Translated Novels</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter1 the great villain system</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>PS: Due to individual reasons in this book, all characters involved in the original work need to be obscured or their names changed.It&amp;rsquo;s not Author - kun&amp;rsquo;s deliberate mistake. Please forgive me.
In the shabby hut, the dim light radiates hazy brilliance, and only a thin figure can be vaguely seen crouching beside the table.
Su Xin&amp;rsquo;er very cautiously holds half of the mouldy steamed bread and swallows.
&amp;ldquo;No! I cannot eat it, this is for the elder brother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter2  can kill people, is the sword!</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>The next morning, Su Xin woke up early and saw Xin&amp;rsquo;er, who was still asleep, quietly covered her with a quilt.
Opening the rice jar, Su Xin&amp;rsquo;s heart felt a little convulsive pain when he saw the rice jar with only a dozen grains of rice inside.
Staggering out of the door, Su Xin planned to find something to make a sword.
Get Jing Wuming&amp;rsquo;s Quick Sword, he also need to have a sword first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter3  If you want to destroy it, you must  make it crazy  first</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Changning Prefecture 49 Blocks, although Long Music Block is the poorest Fang City, but it is not all slums. At least one street is pretty good. It is called Happy Forest.
As the name suggests, Happy Forest is a place where people are happy,On a small street, there are hundreds of gambling halls, restaurants, brothels, and inn.
With this Happy Forest, you can feed dozens of Gangsters from Flying Eagle Gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter4  What I&#39;m better at is the right hand</title>
      <link>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ibig5.net/strongest-boss-system/sbs-chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Outside the drunk moon building, Su Xin looks at the carved beams and painted rafters,Decorated with gilded, it looks luxurious and incomparable architecture exclaimed.
Compared with the grottoes of long music block,It&amp;rsquo;s almost like another world here.
&amp;ldquo;Stop! This is already our Flying Eagle Gang Packing Yard.Go elsewhere.Seeing Su Xin entering Drunk Moon Building, a young Flying Eagle Gang gangster quickly stopped him.
Su Xin said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m here for Liu Sandao.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>