<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The demon is around on Aisan Translated Novels</title>
    <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The demon is around on Aisan Translated Novels</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.ibig5.net/demon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter1 I&#39;m here to save the foreign people in dire straits.</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Chen Zhao (zhao) dragged his suitcase out of the airport.
I have heard that foreign people are living in dire straits, and in line with the idea of saving the world, they must come to save them.
At the gate stood two women, one of whom was Chen Zhao&amp;rsquo;s mother and the other was a white woman who was her assistant, as if her name was Sally.
Chen Zhao is an accident doctor, has had medical malpractice in China, has been unable to engage in related work in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter2 This Shapi is a demon?</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Chen Zhao mentioned Shapi Dog: &amp;ldquo;it is said that a small number of people will have auditory hallucinations after flying, it should be my auditory hallucinations.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Man, you are insulting a hell lord. Do you understand what this means?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;do you know more than a hundred ways for Chinese to cook dog meat?&amp;rdquo; Chen Zhao is not a pussy at all, mainly because his brain has not turned the corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter3 I am the demon lord of our village</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Chen Zhao looked at the metal box on the table. &amp;ldquo;do you know that box?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;what box?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s it.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;which one?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;the one on the table.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;what box is there on the table except the lamp?&amp;rdquo; Bezebub&amp;rsquo;s face was completely at a loss.
Puzzled, Chen Zhao looked at Beelzebub. &amp;ldquo;are you sure you didn&amp;rsquo;t see anything?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Human, there&amp;rsquo;s nothing there?&amp;rdquo;
He or it, really can&amp;rsquo;t see anything.
Is this the metal box?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter4 Be a supernumerary doctor</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Knock-
At night, Chen Zhao heard a quick knock at the door.
&amp;ldquo;what time is it?&amp;rdquo; Chen Zhao opened his eyes in a daze and saw that it was still dark outside the window.
&amp;ldquo;Chen, did you hear that? I&amp;rsquo;m Ethan. &amp;quot;
Chen Zhao smeared up and kicked something under his feet.
Wang-
&amp;ldquo;Man, you stepped on me.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Why haven&amp;rsquo;t you gone back to hell?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to go back yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter5 First customer</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dm-chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>If you want to get a medical license, you need to be familiar with the medical laws and rules on this side of the United States, which is equivalent to a new college entrance examination, which means that, Chen Zhao will not have a stable source of income for a long time to come.
And their own money, certainly not enough to last that long.
So on second thought, Chen Zhao decided to take Ethan&amp;rsquo;s advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter6 Add another right-hand man</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dia-chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dia-chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Chen Zhao was not too surprised. In fact, when he came in, he roughly guessed the situation when he saw the looks of both men and women.
Chen Zhao put on his gloves and grabbed the whole dead Loach. &amp;ldquo;do you feel anything?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;did you take any medicine beforehand?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;do you have the habit of taking medicine? Or are you allergic to some kind of drug? &amp;quot;
&amp;ldquo;No. Asshole, can you do it quickly?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter7 I can&#39;t believe you seduced other demons behind me.</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dia-chapter-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dia-chapter-7/</guid>
      <description>Dale was no longer in a hurry to go to bed and send Chen Zhao off the estate.
&amp;ldquo;Sorry, Chen, it was my fault just now. I hope you can come to my manor sometime. My manor will always be so lively. I think my girls welcome you, too. Of course, including Trilla. &amp;quot;
&amp;ldquo;Thank you. I&amp;rsquo;ll come sometime. &amp;quot; Chen Zhao doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to waste his energy here, but the scene of the wine pool is really tempting, and it looks like he should find a regular date first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter8 Enter the state</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dia-chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dia-chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, but I ate a little too much tonight.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;in China, girls who can eat represent happiness.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;but neither East nor West likes fat girls, do they?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I like plump girls, like you.&amp;rdquo;
Greene is a little thick, but not fat, at least in a category acceptable to Chen Zhao.
&amp;ldquo;what are you looking for?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I suspect my pet is sneaking along with me.&amp;rdquo; Chen Zhao said, because Glenn did eat a little too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chapter9 Conjecture about the crystallization of demons</title>
      <link>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dia-chapter-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ibig5.net/demon/dia-chapter-9/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Thank you for your patronage. It comes to 23 dollars.&amp;rdquo;
Phil checked out, picked up the packed food, and was about to return to the car when he felt stung at his feet.
After two steps, he suddenly felt dizzy, and he reluctantly supported two more steps.
But in the third step, he finally lost his balance.
Phil clenched his teeth, and he had seen that a woman who had been sitting in the corner had stood up and was clearly pulling out her gun.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>